Country Code	Region	IncomeGroup	SpecialNotes	TableName
ABW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Aruba
AFE			"26 countries, stretching from the Red Sea in the North to the Cape of Good Hope in the South (https://www.worldbank.org/en/region/afr/eastern-and-southern-africa)"	Africa Eastern and Southern
AFG	South Asia	Low income	Fiscal year end: March 20; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Afghanistan
AFW			"22 countries, stretching from the westernmost point of Africa, across the equator, and partly along the Atlantic Ocean till the Republic of Congo in the South (https://www.worldbank.org/en/region/afr/western-and-central-africa)"	Africa Western and Central
AGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Angola
ALB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Albania
AND	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Andorra
ARB			Arab World aggregate. Arab World is composed of members of the League of Arab States.	Arab World
ARE	Middle East & North Africa	High income		United Arab Emirates
ARG	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Argentina
ARM	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Armenia
ASM	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		American Samoa
ATG	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Antigua and Barbuda
AUS	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Australia
AUT	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 13.7603 Austrian schilling. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Austria
AZE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Azerbaijan
BDI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Burundi
BEL	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Belgian franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Belgium
BEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Benin
BFA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Burkina Faso
BGD	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Bangladesh
BGR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Bulgaria
BHR	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Bahrain
BHS	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		"Bahamas, The"
BIH	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Bosnia and Herzegovina
BLR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Data before 2015 were adjusted to reflect the new denomination effective from July 1, 2016 (BYN), a decrease of 10,000 times (1 BYN = 10,000 BYR)"	Belarus
BLZ	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		Belize
BMU	North America	High income		Bermuda
BOL	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		Bolivia
BRA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Brazil
BRB	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Barbados
BRN	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Brunei Darussalam
BTN	South Asia	Lower middle income		Bhutan
BWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Botswana
CAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Central African Republic
CAN	North America	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Canada
CEB			Central Europe and the Baltics aggregate.	Central Europe and the Baltics
CHE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Switzerland
CHI	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Channel Islands
CHL	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Chile
CHN	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong; and on 20 December 1999 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China."	China
CIV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Côte d'Ivoire
CMR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Cameroon
COD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		"Congo, Dem. Rep."
COG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		"Congo, Rep."
COL	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Colombia
COM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Comoros
CPV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Cabo Verde
CRI	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Costa Rica
CSS				Caribbean small states
CUB	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Cuba
CUW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Curaçao
CYM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Cayman Islands
CYP	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.585274 Cyprus pounds. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Cyprus
CZE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Czech Republic
DEU	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Germany
DJI	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income		Djibouti
DMA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Dominica
DNK	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Denmark
DOM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Dominican Republic
DZA	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income		Algeria
EAP				East Asia & Pacific (excluding high income)
EAR			Early-dividend countries are mostly lower-middle-income countries further along the fertility transition. Fertility rates have fallen below four births per woman and the working-age share of the population is likely rising considerably.	Early-demographic dividend
EAS			East Asia and Pacific regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	East Asia & Pacific
ECA				Europe & Central Asia (excluding high income)
ECS			Europe and Central Asia regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	Europe & Central Asia
ECU	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Ecuador
EGY	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY for years 1980 and after. The data from 1973 to 1979 are calendar year data.	"Egypt, Arab Rep."
EMU			Euro area aggregate.	Euro area
ERI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Eritrea
ESP	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 166.386 Spanish peseta. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Spain
EST	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2011: 1 euro = 15.6466 Estonian kroon. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Estonia
ETH	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Fiscal year end: July 7; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Ethiopia
EUU			European Union aggregate.	European Union
FCS			"Fragile and conflict-affected situations aggregate.

Countries are distinguished based on the nature and severity of issues they face. The classification uses the following categories:

- Countries with high levels of institutional and social fragility, identified based on publicly available indicators that measure the quality of policy and institutions and manifestations of fragility.
- Countries affected by violent conflict, identified based on a threshold number of conflict-related deaths relative to the population. This category includes two sub-categories based on the intensity of violence: countries in high-intensity conflict and countries in medium-intensity conflict.

For more information, please visit https://www.worldbank.org/en/topic/fragilityconflictviolence/brief/harmonized-list-of-fragile-situations."	Fragile and conflict affected situations
FIN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 5.94573 Finnish markka. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Finland
FJI	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Fiji
FRA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 6.55957 French franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	France
FRO	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Faroe Islands
FSM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Based on the Pacific and Virgin Islands Training Initiative, national accounts data have been revised."	"Micronesia, Fed. Sts."
GAB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Gabon
GBR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		United Kingdom
GEO	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Includes self-governed areas only, which mostly exclude Abkhazia and South Ossetia, but small areas in Abkhazia and South Ossetia are included before 2008 or 2009 because of the changes in self-governed areas."	Georgia
GHA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Ghana
GIB	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Gibraltar
GIN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Guinea
GMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		"Gambia, The"
GNB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Guinea-Bissau
GNQ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Equatorial Guinea
GRC	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 340.75 Greek drachma. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Greece
GRD	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Grenada
GRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Greenland
GTM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Guatemala
GUM	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Guam
GUY	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Guyana
HIC			"High income group aggregate. High-income economies are those in which 2020 GNI per capita was $12,696 or more."	High income
HKG	East Asia & Pacific	High income	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China. Agriculture value added includes mining and quarrying."	"Hong Kong SAR, China"
HND	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		Honduras
HPC			Heavily indebted poor countries aggregate.	Heavily indebted poor countries (HIPC)
HRV	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Croatia
HTI	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Haiti
HUN	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Hungary
IBD			IBRD only group aggregate.	IBRD only
IBT			"IDA and IBRD total group aggregate (includes IDA only, IDA blend, and IBRD only)."	IDA & IBRD total
IDA			IDA total group aggregate (includes IDA only and IDA blend).	IDA total
IDB			IDA blend group aggregate.	IDA blend
IDN	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Data for Indonesia include Timor-Leste through 1999 unless otherwise noted.	Indonesia
IDX			IDA only group aggregate.	IDA only
IMN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national account data: FY. Classification for years after 2012 was adjusted and figures were re-estimated by the World Bank, based on the detailed data published by the Cabinet Office, and are not consistent with data for 2011 and before."	Isle of Man
IND	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	India
IRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 0.787564 Irish pound. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Ireland
IRN	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 20; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	"Iran, Islamic Rep."
IRQ	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income		Iraq
ISL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Iceland
ISR	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Israel
ITA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 1936.27 Italian lira. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Italy
JAM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Jamaica
JOR	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income		Jordan
JPN	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Japan
KAZ	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Kazakhstan
KEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Kenya
KGZ	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Kyrgyz Republic
KHM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Cambodia
KIR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Kiribati
KNA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		St. Kitts and Nevis
KOR	East Asia & Pacific	High income		"Korea, Rep."
KWT	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Kuwait
LAC				Latin America & Caribbean (excluding high income)
LAO	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Lao PDR
LBN	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income		Lebanon
LBR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Liberia
LBY	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income		Libya
LCA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		St. Lucia
LCN				Latin America & Caribbean
LDC				Least developed countries: UN classification
LIC			"Low income group aggregate. Low-income economies are those in which 2020 GNI per capita was $1,045 or less."	Low income
LIE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Liechtenstein
LKA	South Asia	Lower middle income		Sri Lanka
LMC			"Lower middle income group aggregate. Lower-middle-income economies are those in which 2020 GNI per capita was between $1,046 and $4,095."	Lower middle income
LMY				Low & middle income
LSO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Lesotho
LTE				Late-demographic dividend
LTU	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2015: 1 euro = 3.45280 Lithuanian litas. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries. Based on data from EUROSTAT, the new reference year is 2010."	Lithuania
LUX	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Luxembourg franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Luxembourg
LVA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2014: 1 euro = 0.702804 Latvian lats. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries. Based on data from EUROSTAT, the new reference year is 2010."	Latvia
MAC	East Asia & Pacific	High income	"On 20 December 1999 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China."	"Macao SAR, China"
MAF	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		St. Martin (French part)
MAR	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income		Morocco
MCO	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Monaco
MDA	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Excluding Transnistria. For 1950-94, World Bank estimates using UN World Population Prospects' growth rates of whole Moldova."	Moldova
MDG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Madagascar
MDV	South Asia	Upper middle income		Maldives
MEA			Middle East and North Africa regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	Middle East & North Africa
MEX	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Mexico
MHL	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Marshall Islands
MIC			"Middle income group aggregate. Middle-income economies are those in which 2020 GNI per capita was between $1,046 and $12,695."	Middle income
MKD	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		North Macedonia
MLI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Mali
MLT	Middle East & North Africa	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.4293 Maltese lira. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries. National accounts data source from 1995 to 2015 is Eurostat; prior to 1995 is UN. The new reference year is 2010."	Malta
MMR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Myanmar
MNA				Middle East & North Africa (excluding high income)
MNE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005."	Montenegro
MNG	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Mongolia
MNP	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Northern Mariana Islands
MOZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Mozambique
MRT	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	National account data were adjusted to reflect the new banknote (1 new ouguiya = 10 old ouguiya)	Mauritania
MUS	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Mauritius
MWI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Malawi
MYS	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Malaysia
NAC			North America regional aggregate. There are no economies in North America classified as low or middle income.	North America
NAM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Namibia
NCL	East Asia & Pacific	High income		New Caledonia
NER	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Niger
NGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Nigeria
NIC	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		Nicaragua
NLD	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 2.20371 Netherlands guilder. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Netherlands
NOR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Norway
NPL	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: July 14; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Nepal
NRU	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Nauru
NZL	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	New Zealand
OED				OECD members
OMN	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Oman
OSS				Other small states
PAK	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Pakistan
PAN	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Panama
PER	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Peru
PHL	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Philippines
PLW	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Palau
PNG	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Papua New Guinea
POL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Poland
PRE			"Pre-dividend countries are mostly low-income countries, lagging in key human development indicators and with current fertility levels above four births per woman. They face very rapid population growth."	Pre-demographic dividend
PRI	Latin America & Caribbean	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Puerto Rico
PRK	East Asia & Pacific	Low income		"Korea, Dem. People's Rep."
PRT	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 200.482 Portuguese escudo. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Portugal
PRY	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Paraguay
PSE	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income		West Bank and Gaza
PSS			Pacific island small states aggregate.	Pacific island small states
PST			Post-dividend countries are mostly high-income countries where fertility has transitioned below replacement levels.	Post-demographic dividend
PYF	East Asia & Pacific	High income		French Polynesia
QAT	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Qatar
ROU	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Romania
RUS	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Russian Federation
RWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Rwanda
SAS				South Asia
SAU	Middle East & North Africa	High income		Saudi Arabia
SDN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Sudan
SEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Senegal
SGP	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Singapore
SLB	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Solomon Islands
SLE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Sierra Leone
SLV	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		El Salvador
SMR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		San Marino
SOM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Somalia
SRB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators, such as those series for which data appear only for Serbia and not Montenegro--e.g., aid, environment, external debt, balance of payments, various social indicators excluding population--continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005. Moreover, data from 1999 onward for Serbia for most indicators exclude data for Kosovo, 1999 being the year when Kosovo became a territory under international administration pursuant to UN Security Council Resolution 1244 (1999); any exceptions are noted. Kosovo became a World Bank member on June 29, 2009; available data are shown separately for Kosovo. In 2011, the Statistical Office of Serbia improved the methodology of national accounts data for 2003 onward. Specifically, the classification of sectors was revised."	Serbia
SSA				Sub-Saharan Africa (excluding high income)
SSD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	South Sudan
SSF			Sub-Saharan Africa regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	Sub-Saharan Africa
SST			Small states (members of the Small States Forum) aggregate.	Small states
STP	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	National account data were adjusted to reflect the new banknote (1 new Dobra STN = 1000 old Dobra STD)	São Tomé and Principe
SUR	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Suriname
SVK	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2009: 1 euro = 30.126 Slovak koruna. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Slovak Republic
SVN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2007: 1 euro = 239.64 Slovenian tolar. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Slovenia
SWE	Europe & Central Asia	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Sweden
SWZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Authorities revised national accounts from 1999 to 2015.	Eswatini
SXM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Sint Maarten (Dutch part)
SYC	Sub-Saharan Africa	High income		Seychelles
SYR	Middle East & North Africa	Low income		Syrian Arab Republic
TCA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Turks and Caicos Islands
TCD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Chad
TEA			East Asia & Pacific (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	East Asia & Pacific (IDA & IBRD)
TEC			Europe & Central Asia (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Europe & Central Asia (IDA & IBRD)
TGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Togo
THA	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Thailand
TJK	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Tajikistan
TKM	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Turkmenistan
TLA			Latin America & the Caribbean (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Latin America & Caribbean (IDA & IBRD)
TLS	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Timor-Leste
TMN			Middle East & North Africa (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Middle East & North Africa (IDA & IBRD)
TON	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Tonga
TSA			South Asia (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	South Asia (IDA & IBRD)
TSS			Sub-Saharan Africa (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Sub-Saharan Africa (IDA & IBRD)
TTO	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Trinidad and Tobago
TUN	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income		Tunisia
TUR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Turkey
TUV	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Tuvalu
TZA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Tanzania
UGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Uganda
UKR	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Ukraine
UMC			"Upper middle income group aggregate. Upper-middle-income economies are those in which 2020 GNI per capita was between $4,096 and $12,695."	Upper middle income
URY	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Uruguay
USA	North America	High income		United States
UZB	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Uzbekistan
VCT	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		St. Vincent and the Grenadines
VEN	Latin America & Caribbean			"Venezuela, RB"
VGB	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		British Virgin Islands
VIR	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Virgin Islands (U.S.)
VNM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Vietnam
VUT	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Vanuatu
WLD			World aggregate.	World
WSM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year ends on June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Samoa
XKX	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Kosovo
YEM	Middle East & North Africa	Low income		"Yemen, Rep."
ZAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	South Africa
ZMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"National accounts data were rebased to reflect the January 1, 2013, introduction of the new Zambian kwacha at a rate of 1,000 old kwacha = 1 new kwacha."	Zambia
ZWE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"National Accounts data are in Zimbabwean Dollar (ZWL). Before 2017, one ZWL is set to be equal to one USD."	Zimbabwe
